{
    "id": "960b7433e944488f877356d1b2a4f829",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We have few reasons ............................... staying.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "30414dd846f24a04894a8b4515a2321c"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is little point ................................. doing anything about it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "40b0a9c2e7494769815c4b35bea5ebbd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is ................................ the phone?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f7b18b87dc0049bd8baac622d0dd4195"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you like to come ............................... me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "92b65f93539a4127b8cef49c5f62bc64"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you send me the bill ................................... the repairs?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "132319d60dbb4cf7a9ef16f5bd63a6d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "We live many miles ................................ the city.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ad87051c4e364dfe96f06714f5f87252"
        },
        {
            "question": "He will have gone .............................. now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "by",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db1d8902153e4529823b76362a5d3688"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you happy to work ................................... weekends?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fbacf13190144671aabd43397f465f1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer you to call me .................................. my first name.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d1d1104e25de4ae3840377621dcf3399"
        },
        {
            "question": "You shouldn't speak like that ................................ your grandparents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "44560ed12f784b55b1f009765588e59d"
        },
        {
            "question": "For dinner I had leftovers .............................. lunch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "to",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a3e780697da44b79b4f0c3c005dd43e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think it is a good idea ....................................... him to find another job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3e655a74c7e5413b8d1deb75bfebffc4"
        }
    ]
}